You seem smart enough to understand, you saw right through my ruse
You're not like those fools at my old cult. They were weaklings, mentally frail sheep
They were mine, body and soul. I gave them hope and excitement, it was so easy
They all died believing they were going to paradise
Some rubbish I made up because I was sick of dealing with their neediness
For a while it was nice to feel like a god. These people did everything for me
You can't even imagine the things I've made them do in my name
Unfortunately for them the excitement wore off and only boredom remained
I had an escape plan after making them take the paradise pills but things just didn't work out
So here am I now in this freak show. I don't even know what the point of all this is
Why did they even bring you here?