We've arrived at the final challenge
But before we move on to that I'd like to just get a few things off my chest
You know just a bit ago when I took you to that room where I first asked for your help?
I was actually a part of Locke's research team
And I had snuck that secret room in the simulation myself but it seems Locke found out about it
I was naive to think they would never find it
All this time I tried to be secretive and pretended to cooperate
I wanted to keep my family safe... in case they are still even alive but I fucked it all up
You must be wondering why I ended up here
I was a top ranking researcher, only second to Dr Locke
I thought I was making a difference, you know...
Really important work
Doing cutting edge research for all of mankind
We were tasked by the elite to develop a solution for transferring the human consciousness into the virtual world
As a means of escaping the next grand extinction event on earth
The public is completely unaware but twenty years from now and I know it sounds like something out of a movie
A giant meteor will actually fall on earth
The impact, subsequent natural catastrophes and atmosphere changes will annihilate us all
Some remote islands off the pacific were calculated to be left mostly untouched
I was a fool and thought they were going to try to save everyone
But eventually I discovered that they had handpicked a couple thousand to be the last stand of humanity
While leaving everyone else to die
Of the privileged chosen those who would prefer to do so would continue their biological existence
Living peacefully in the small pacific islands with an artificial atmosphere isolated from the rest of the planet
Procreating to keep the population in relatively stable numbers whilst maintaining the technology needed to run the simulation for those who wish to be virtually immortalized
I was horrified and disgusted by these self aggrandizing parasites trying to play the hand of god
Even though my family was guaranteed survival at the end of the world I still could not let it stand
I was preparing to expose them but as you can surmise… my cover was blown
Those bastards killed two birds with one stone, they forcefully used me as the very first test subject for human virtualization